Viewers, ask Jesus to locate you in His Mercy.
Locate me in Your mercy, Lord and deliver me!
Locate me in Your mercy and heal me, Lord!
Locate me in You mercy and free me!
Lord, Jesus, locate me in Your mercy and free me!
Locate me in Your mercy and deliver me!
Locate me in Your mercy and free me!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Mercy!
Locate me in Your mercy and heal me!
Locate me in Your mercy and deliver me!
You are declared free in the name of Jesus!
Wherever it is located in your body,
Hear the voice of God!
Where can you go from His presence?
You sickness, where can you go from His presence?
You affliction, where can you go from His presence?
Whatever name they call it - never a
sickness Jesus cannot heal.
You cancer, affliction - leave my people,
in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name!
You are declared free, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Begin to talk in your freedom.
Jesus says, "You are healed!"
You are healed!
I say, "You are healed!"
TT: lizz ndungu
Date : 27/10/2018
TT: Juliet Bwalya, 28/09/18